[Music]
I'm rames ay and I'm a life insurance
adviser with ad sunlife uh insurance for
the last 22 years I was into traditional
businesses I was into distribution and
uh in Telecom business and also into
other uh businesses in the traditional
space but this business gives me lot of
freedom uh for my time for my uh energy
the value what I say is uh know it's
called Roy return on time invested it's
very high when you compare to any other
profession or any business that's the
reason uh one of the reasons I'm
continuing uh with this profession and
it's a very very Noble profession
compared to lot of other professions but
this is the only profession where we
feel okay our client should be healthy
you know their family should be very uh
healthy and they should not have any
Financial uh burden just in case is uh
the earning earning member uh dice okay
so I feel this is a very very Noble
profession and anyone can uh come in and
uh take this profession forward that's
another uh reason for me to continue in
this journey